I've been on a date just once. It was back when I was in junior high.
I got dressed up and went out with a boy. That was all.
I ate a crepe in Harajuku. It's what everyone does.
But if the person next to me was the actual real him,
then it would have meant the whole world to me.
Thinking back on it, I'm sure it wasn't really a date, since he was all I could think about.
It was sort of like we were just playing pretend.
I can't even recall the name of the boy I went on a date with.
I'm sorry. It was awful of me.
How elegant.
Oh, you're up early, Noriko. Doesn't your summer vacation start today?
Dad, please! Don't ruin this for me!
What? How am I ruining it?
You're ruining the elegant mood I've created in here!
You are such a dedicated child when it comes to acting out your little fantasies.
Putting together all of your accessories and clothing seems like so much work.
And so what? I'm doing all of this work for myself, Kate! Just go away!
But come on! I want some breakfast too!
That's right. Today is a very important day for me.
After all, I want to make sure I look the prettiest ever in my life.
That's partly for him to be mesmerized.
But who am I kidding?
It's mostly for myself.
Not for anyone else.
What I do is only for myself to enjoy.
That's how everyone should be, really.
Where do you want to go?
Nobody should have to find replacements.
That is, for the important people that they hold dear in their lives.
Ah, Hanabi, are your ears pierced?
Huh? No, they're not pierced. These are just clip-ons.
Ah. Why aren't they pierced?
Because I'm scared of all the pain.
You know, that kind of turned me on.
What are you talking about?
Jeez, what are you looking at?
Hey, cut it out. Give me back my phone.
Stop it, will you? Give it back.
Just kidding. I didn't look at it.
Aren't you forward?
Ow!
Let's go to the hotel now. Come on. I'm sorry.
I'm not going there.
Then we'll just go to a hotel as a reward.
Reward for what? I'm not going.
Why does he have to mess with my head?
You know you want to.
Really?
Is that all you could ever think about?
Is your head just filled with sex 24-7?
Yep. That's pretty much it.
I mean, I'm a man, aren't I? So, yeah.
That's not a good reason.
It is.
Don't underestimate the sex drive.
I just want to...
If you tease me too much, then I'm just...
Yeah? Hello?
Liar.
What do you say?
You said we could take it slow and get to know each other.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Sorry.
I'm going to split now.
Who was that?
A girl who's going to let me do her.
See ya.
Hey!
Hold on!
You're stretching my shirt.
I'm so sorry.
Uh, are you sure about this?
I mean, it's the movie I want to see.
You might think it's too boring.
Hmm.
But you'll like it.
Come on, let's go.
I...
I want to hold his hand.
But for now...
Hold on!
Yeah, sure. Okay.
All you need to do is turn and look at me.
That's all I need.
I am truly happy.
There's nobody else in here.
Uh, yeah.
I guess there's not.
What now?
I'm the one who wanted to see this.
But I can't seem to pay attention at all.
It's because it's just really Mookie and I here all alone together.
I didn't know that a theater could bring us so close.
I've loved you.
For all my life.
I never knew how wonderful it is to be in love.
Hmm.
What about a love that never happens?
Is it just misery?
It's okay, though.
I love you enough to live with that.
Mookie?
That's not true.
Even if it never blossoms, love is...
Oh, that's a lie.
If there's not a happy ending, then I don't want it.
That was pretty good, huh?
Really?
Thank goodness.
What do you mean, thank goodness?
Uh, I mean...
I would have felt bad if you didn't like it, since I was the one that picked it out and everything.
If it ended up boring, then it would have been the movie's fault.
It's not something you should worry about.
I...
I love him.
Mookie?
I wonder how he felt about what I did.
Hey, Mookie?
Did you know, if you go to sleep holding hands, you will both have the same dream?
I want so badly to tell him, but I can't do it.
It's as if I'm in a dream right now.
Mocha.
I'm hungry.
Let's get some food.
Thank goodness.
I'm still dreaming.
Mm-hmm.
Why did I do that?
Why did I stop him in the first place?
Hey, hold on!
What?
You let me do you?
No, I...
Um...
Later.
I chased after him like an idiot, but it didn't work.
In the end, he just left me anyway.
Now all I'm left with is my stubborn pride.
That's all.
I never got him to fall in love with me.
Only lust over me.
But I was fine with that.
It's not like I can tell the difference.
Love or lust, they all feel the same to me now.
I want to be obsessed over her.
I want all their desires.
I won't give them anything.
And I won't let them take anything from me either.
It can't be equal.
Please, someone.
I don't care who.
I just want you to...
I want you to think I'm worth something.
This is pathetic.
Since when did I become this sort of woman?
At first, I just thought...
I wanted to be with the person I loved.
But why, God?
Why is it like this?
Why does unrequited love always leave you feeling so empty?
I want to see you.
Let's meet.
Is that your phone?
You can answer it.
Uh, no.
It's fine.
Please, you don't need to hold back on my account.
What am I saying?
This is not enough.
Just smile.
I had fun today, didn't I?
Aren't I satisfied?
So I should just smile.
Go on.
It tastes good, doesn't it?
Because soon, I'll eventually realize it's nothing but a silly dream.
I can't believe it's still muggy now.
Thanks for staying out so late with me.
I, um...
That was fun, Mookie.
Yeah?
I'm glad I realized it halfway through.
That's right.
If it's not going to happen,
then I just need to give myself good memories.
I can recreate the perfect dream
and just hold on to it,
playing it back over and over again.
I'll watch it forever.
It'll just be mild.
Hey, Mocha.
What's wrong?
Something happened?
You're acting strange.
Do you realize how long it's been
since you actually looked at me today?
I was about to make a horrible mistake
I couldn't take back.
If he had rejected me when our hands touched,
I would have just died.
I wouldn't have been able to go on.
I can keep on living my life
without a real love to call my own.
Hey.
Mookie, I had a lot of fun today.
I'm truly thankful.
I'll cherish this.
This memory is forever mine.
I can continue living in an endless dream
that isn't real.
I can make that come true by myself.
And I...
I know...
I can...
be happy.
I love you.
Mookie.
And like that,
the princess' kiss shatters the dream I had built up.
And the princess finally awakes to find
she's left in darkness.
And the reason she doesn't cry herself hoarse
is because she has not yet learned
sadness nor happiness.
I'm tired.
There's nobody I want to see.
I hate men.
I can't see Sanai.
A friend.
I don't have any friends.
Oh well.
Sometimes I do feel like just being alone.
It's been a while
since I've been in here.
When was the last time?
It smells nice.
Mocha,
sorry you didn't have fun.
I did have fun.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
But it was lacking
as much as it was fun,
I guess you could say.
I wonder why.
I pretend I don't know,
even though I do.
You wanna know?
I don't know.
I see.
I know.
I've known for a while now.
Well then,
good night, Noriko.
Okay.
Good night, Mama.
Dear perfect god in all of heaven,
please let Mookie and I
be married and live in Versailles one day.
I don't wanna go live there.
I'd rather be in Himeji Castle.
A shogun is way better than a prince.
I wish I could grow a mustache.
You want me to be the prince
in this play of yours?
Not interested.
I'm fine being a tree.
Trees are always nice and big.
I'd like to go to Yakushima.
No way!
You and I are going to England and France
for our honeymoon,
and that's final,
you hear me?
This is pointless.
You and I just don't match.
We're breaking up the band, Mocha.
Not that we had one.
Oh, my sweetie.
What's the matter?
There, there, dear.
Hey, I'm sorry for being mean.
Please don't cry.
We won't break up the band.
Really?
I, I love you.
All right, fine.
I already knew back then
that I would always be given a free pass.
There was never an adult
who didn't cave in when I cried.
Like I said,
I already knew then.
I knew it was all an act.
I'd never be the pure princess
you find in books.
I've known that for a while now
and took advantage of it.
Much to my shame
and regret.
But I'm going to stop playing cute
from now on.
I'm scared to go in this new direction.
My love for Mookie
should be more genuine
than I'm trying to make it.
It may be a front,
but he's not mine.
He's someone else's
and I must stop.
But this is the real me
finally coming out.
I know that now.
Then how are you
any different
from all the other people
supposedly in love?
You should stop this right now.
If you truly love him,
you would.
You're wrong about that.
I was the one
who didn't know anything
about love.
He has to see you
for who you are
or it won't end
the way you want.
Can you really live with that?
Stop.
I want to touch him now.
I should have done this
to him a long time ago.
I mean,
it's not that I don't care
about the future at all,
but I...
I realized
there's nothing greater
than having a person you love
wanting you back.
It's the best feeling.
This electric response,
this heat,
in this very moment,
you belong only to me.
Now that I know
this sweet taste,
I can never turn back.
I want to be filled.
Tell me, Mookie,
is this what you do
with her?
Wild, do you
not like it?
I'm sorry,
but I...
I'm just not
really sure why.
But
you're just so damn cute
right now.
That's right.
I am cute,
so it's okay.
I can live
with just this.
You don't have to say
you love me.
I can live on
because he says
I'm cute.
I love you,
Mookie,
so much.
I don't need
his answer.
I've never seen
a shooting star.
I thought it was
fate nudging me,
so I made
a little wish.
If I make this
stick in with
just the one shot,
then I'll get
the courage.
girls can be
so cute.
I even like
how they can be
so unpredictable.
Want to keep going?
I'll stop
if you want.
I don't want
to stop.
Do you
love me?
Why?
My God.
Why do I have
to be such a coward
all the time?
I can't go further
without checking
with them first.
Wait a sec.
Mocha,
how does this
come off?
You just
have to undo
the ribbon first.
Yeah,
I get it.
So like this,
then?
Seriously?
No,
please.
What do you
mean,
no?
Show me.
I really
hate my breasts.
Why?
You
won't compare
them?
I promise.
I won't.
I want to see them.
Because they're yours.
What am I saying?
I'm going straight to hell.
Can I touch?
It's dark enough in here.
Can't even see them.
But honestly,
in the end,
that's not it.
I'm sorry.
the reason I can't sleep with her
is for myself.
Same reason I can't get past it either.
But you're too important.
Do you understand that?
You always will be to me.
I know that already.
I get it.
I know that I'm special to you
in your own warped way of thinking.
I understand.
I'm sacred.
An ornament that can't ever be touched.
But it's dumb.
I want to be touched all over by you.
I don't care what happens to me.
I don't care if I'm not pure.
I just want to live in a world
where you can touch me.
If you can't give me at least that,
then what's the point of being special?
Why am I arguing with him?
I don't want it.
This doesn't help me achieve
what I do want.
The fact that I can't just throw it away
is proof of my attachment.
That's not it.
It's the only thing
that's been holding me up
all these years.
I don't know how to let go.
It was something I treasured.
Right.
I'm done here.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
Neither of us pushed for it.
We just decided to meet.
Both of us finally getting the courage
to maybe talk.
I made a decision.
Let's tell them how we really feel
and before summer vacation ends.
So then,
we decided we would both get rejected
and be cleansed of our pain
before summer vacation ended.
Then we could start an actual relationship
and hold each other's hands
on proper dates.
We should have done this
much sooner than this.
This took us way too long.
Hey,
we're only doing it
because we have nothing to lose.
Look at us.
Why are we such pathetic cowards?
Shut your mouth.
Although,
who knows what the future holds.
We might end up happy.
We'll be right back.
We'll get ready.